TITLE Introduction
BIGBOX HTML (HyperText Markup Language) is the coding language that drives the web — every single website you've ever visited is powered by HTML.  Specifically, HTML defines the structure of the web page, creating a skeleton of all the elements on the page, which can then be styled using another web language, CSS.  This tutorial will primarily focus on HTML, but on occasion will include a few basic CSS concepts to guide our HTML work.

The HTML language is standardized by the W3C (World Wide Web Consortium), however there are some minor differences between web browsers.  What works on one browser may not work perfectly on the next.  This tutorial will touch on a few ways to ensure consistency between the major web browsers.

HTML has evolved numerous times since its introduction in 1993.  This tutorial will teach the most modern and widely adopted version of HTML, HTML5.

Good luck and happy coding!

Note: This tutorial uses HTML Tidy, software developed by the HTACG, a working group of the W3C.
END