TITLE Attributes
LBOX Recall from the Tags and Elements lesson that within the angle brackets of a tag you can store some information about an element.  Attributes are how we do that.  Attributes are what we would call key and value pairs — every attribute has two parts, a name (key) and a value.  You can't have two of the same attribute on a tag and an attribute can only have one value.  Attributes are also only on opening tags, not closing tags.  Here is the basic "template" of an element with attributes.
<tag attributeKey="value" differentKey="value5"> content </tag>

There are many different attributes, and they are often specific to whatever kind of tag you're using.  For example, a link will have the href attribute (the value for an href is the URL the link points to), while a text box should not have an href.  There are several important ones that apply almost everywhere.

Let's look at the id and class attributes.  These are actually fairly similar and will be very, very helpful for when you use CSS and JavaScript on your webpage.  An ID is a unique identifier for an element.  You can only have one ID for an element, and no other element on the ID can share the same ID.  IDs must be at least one character and can't contain any whitespace (no spaces, tabs, or anything like that).  Class is the exact same thing except it is not unique - multiple elements can have the same class.

The style attribute allows you to apply CSS styles to your code.  In the example code, the style attribute tells the browser that the div will be exactly 250 pixels wide and 100 pixels tall.  For production code, most of the time you should not use this attribute and use a separate CSS file instead.  But for our purposes in this tutorial it's okay.

A note on coding style: as you can see in the example code, if an element is empty (it has no content, ie, nothing between the opening and closing tags), the closing tag does not necessarily need to be on a new line.  But most of the time it isn't wrong if you put the closing tag on a new line anyway.  These are just little things you'll pick up on as you get exposed to more and more code.
END
SCBOX HTML READONLY
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
  <title>Attributes!</title>
</head>
<body>
  <p id="first"></p>
  <p id="2nd"></p>
  <div class="DarkBlueBox" style="height:100px; width:250px"></div>
  <form class="DarkBlueBox"></form>
</body>
</html>
END