TITLE Quiz - Style
LBOX Now that you know a little about HTML, elements, and coding style, it's time to put your knowledge to the test.  The code on the right is malformed!  Your task is to fix it so it is valid, well-formatted HTML code.  Here are a few things to remember as you solve this task:

1) All HTML files require 4 basic tags

2) Well-formed HTML code will be properly indented.  Use two spaces to indent.

Good luck!
END
SCBOX HTML
<html>
<body><h1>Yikes!</h1>
</body></html>
END
CCBUTTON
StyleCheck
END