TITLE Tags and Elements
LBOX Tags and Elements are the basic units of HTML.  There are many different tags, but there are some important things that they (mostly) all share. (Just like in English or other languages, the rules of HTML syntax come with a few exceptions.)  Tags come in pairs: there is an "opening tag" and a "closing tag," and there can be stuff in between them, like more tags, or just plain text.  Tags and some information about them are bound within angle brackets (< and >).  A closing tag will always end with a forward slash (/) before the greater than sign.  The opening tag, closing tag, and the content between them are what we refer to as elements.

Let's look at a few examples.  The HTML tag encapsulates all the other HTML code in the document.  The second line of your HTML document should be the opening HTML tag, <html>, and the last line should be the closing tag, </html>.  As you can see in the example code on the right, all the other tags go between the opening and closing HTML tags.

There are two main sections to an HTML document:  the head and the body.  These are defined in the <head> and <body> tags, respectively.  (See the example code.)  The head contains information about the document, such as search keywords, associated files, etc.  The most common tag in the head is the title tag, which defines the text at the top of the browser tab.  Our example code currently has a blank title.  We could define one by typing our title between the tags like so:
<title>My Web Page</title>

The body contains everything that is seen. Text, images, links, colorful boxes — all of that is defined in the body.  Our example code currently has an empty body, meaning if you open the page in your browser you will just see a blank page. (Throughout the tutorial, you can press the "Run Code" button to see your code in your web browser.  Go ahead and try it!)

So, why is our example code just a blank page?  What we have here is the minimum code you need for an HTML page.  Every single HTML document should contain a Doctype and HTML, head, title, and body tags.  We need to add content (elements, text, images, etc.) or define some styles to have more than just a blank page.
END
SCBOX HTML READONLY
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
  <title></title>
</head>
<body>
</body>
</html>
END
RCBUTTON basic.html