TITLE Coding Style
LBOX An important thing you need to be thinking about as you code is readability.  You and other programmers should be able to read your code.  For example, if you had a 500-line HTML document, and you did no indenting at all, someone is going to have a real problem when they try to edit or fix something on your web page.

So let's define a few ground rules.  First, it is a great idea to indent, as it helps make tag nesting obvious.  Nesting is whenever you have a tag that goes inside a tag.  Whenever you have nested tags, the inside tags should be indented compared to the outside tags.  Take a look at our example code.  The <div> tag is inside the <body> tag, so it gets indented two spaces.  The <form> tag is inside the <div> tag, so it gets indented two more spaces for a total of four spaces.  (You might notice that in the body there are some new elements.  You will learn what they mean later, but for now just take note of how they are indented.)

There are two main exceptions to the indentation rule: <head> and <body>.  The point of idententation is to explicitly show tag nesting, but web developers will just assume that the <head> and <body> within the <html> tag, and so they aren't indented.

Nesting gives us some new terminology.  A parent element is the outer element that contains other elements inside it.  For example, the <div> element is the parent of two <p> tags and a <form> tag.  Here we would similarly say that the two <p> tags and the <form> tag are child elements (children) of the <div> tag.  The two <p> tags and the <form> tag are also siblings of each other.

But back to style, one last thing.  Let's put new tags (both opening and ending tags) on new lines.  If all our tags were just one never ending line, it would be pretty difficult to read.  There are a few exceptions to this rule, such as one-line <p> tags, but we will discuss these later.
END
SCBOX HTML READONLY
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
  <title></title>
</head>
<body>
  <div>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <form>
      <span></span>
    </form>
  </div>
</body>
</html>
END