TITLE Quiz - Basic Document
LBOX We've learned about Doctype, tags and elements, and the four tags needed for an HTML document.  Now it's time to check your understanding, as these concepts are fundamental.  Your task is to write the minimum HTML Document.  
(This is exactly the same as the example code in the Doctype lesson, but you should try to make it yourself before you refer back to the example code.)

This is our first coding exercise, so let's go over how to work with the code editor.  For quizzes, the box on the right is now editable.  Type in your code.  When you press enter at the end of a line, it will also update the colors (the colors are what's known as "syntax highlighting").  When you are done, press the Check button to submit your code.  If there are errors, try to understand them the best you can to fix your code.  You have unlimited tries, because after all the point of these exercises is to help you learn.
END
SCBOX HTML
END
CCBUTTON
END