TITLE Quiz - The Basics
LBOX You've now reached the end of this section!  Before we move on to new material, you have another task.  This assignment will synthesize a lot of what you've learned so far — the basic HTML document, tags, style, and coding style.

The box on the right is blank right now.  Your job is to write an HTML document that contains a <p> tag nested inside a <div> tag.  The <div> tag should have the class "myDiv" and the style "height:100px;".  The <p> tag should have the ID "text".  Good luck!
END
SCBOX HTML
END
CCBUTTON
StyleCheck
contains p(id="text") > div(class="myDiv"|style="height:100px;") > body()
END
RCBUTTON