TITLE Doctype
LBOX There are several elements which every HTML document needs, and the first is called the Doctype.  The Doctype tells the web browser what version of HTML you're using.  The first line of every HTML file must specify the Doctype.  In our case, we are using HTML5, and so our Doctype is super simple.  Look on the first line of our example code on the right.  If we had decided to use HTML4.01 and not HTML5, it would instead look like this:

<!DOCTYPE HTML PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD HTML 4.01 Transitional//EN"
"http://www.w3.org/TR/html4/loose.dtd">

Really messy, right?  So with HTML5 we just stick with this simple rule: the first line should always be:
<!DOCTYPE html>
END
SCBOX HTML READONLY
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
  <title></title>
</head>
<body>
</body>
</html>
END